{
  "title": "電子レンジクイズ",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "q01",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_o.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_k.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_a.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_p.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "q02",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_p.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_q.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_b.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_o.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "q03",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_l.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_c.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_k.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_o.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "q04",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_t.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_u.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_d.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_l.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "q05",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_e.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_p.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_t.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_k.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "q06",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_f.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_n.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_k.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_r.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "q07",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_t.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_n.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_u.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_g.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "q08",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_u.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_p.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_h.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_m.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "q09",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_u.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_o.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_l.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_i.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "q10",
      "prompt": "電子レンジに入れてはいけないものはどれ？",
      "sub": "",
      "options": [
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_l.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_s.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ禁止/q01_j.webp"
        },
        {
          "img": "../電子レンジ可能/q01_u.webp"
        }
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}